dotnet247.com 2003-12-13

# Matthew Reynolds' .NET 247 : The first, independent .NET Programmers Reference

**.NET 247 is owned and operated by RedPiranha.com Ltd.**  
Registered in England number 3894116 

**PRIVACY POLICY**

RedPiranha.com Ltd. is committed to protecting your privacy and to developing technology that gives you the most powerful and secure online experience. This privacy statement explains data collection and use practices of the **.NET 247** site (the “Site”) hosted by RedPiranha.com Ltd. it does not apply to other online or offline RedPiranha.com Ltd. sites, products or services. By accessing the Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement. 

**Collecting Your Personal Information**  
We will collect personal information if you choose to subscribe to the .NET 247 newsletter. The personal information we collect may include your name, e-mail, and/or work phone, work or home address, company or organization name,. 

When you visit the Site, certain anonymous information about your visit is automatically captured. This information may include the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. None of this information is personally-identifiable. This anonymous information is used to help improve the Site, analyze trends, and administer the Site, and is discarded when this process is completed. 

**Use of your Personal Information**  
We use your personal information for the following purposes: 

  * To provide demographic results to our advertisers. We never provide personal information about our visitors to our advertisers or any other third-party, but we do provide aggregated information regarding to professions and/or geographic data of our visitors. 
  * To send you our periodic newsletter should you choose to receive it.. 

RedPiranha.com Ltd. occasionally hires other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering prizes, answering customer questions about products and services, sending postal mail, and sending information about our products, special offers, and other new services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. 

RedPiranha.com Ltd. may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served to RedPiranha.com, Ltd., or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of RedPiranha.com Ltd. and our family of Web sites; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of RedPiranha.com Ltd., our Web sites, or the public. 

Personally identifiable information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which RedPiranha.com Ltd. or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

**Control of your Personal Information**  
Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide on this site will not be shared outside of RedPiranha.com Ltd. and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission. It will only be used for the purposes stated above. 

Please be aware that this Privacy Statement and the choices you make on the Site will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to RedPiranha.com Ltd. in the context of other, separately operated, RedPiranha.com, Ltd. products or services. 

**Access to your Personal Information**  
Customer information is collected by RedPiranha.com Ltd. It is stored at RedPiranha.com Ltd. You can review and change this information by e-mailing us at [hello@dotnet247.com](mailto:hello@dotnet247.com).   

**Security of your Personal Information**  
RedPiranha.com Ltd. strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. Data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction. 

**Cookies**  
We use cookies on this Site to ensure the integrity of the Web Site. We use a session cookie, meaning it expires soon after you leave the Web Site, and is not placed on your hard drive. 

**Links to Other Web sites**  
This Site may contain links to other Web sites. Please be aware that this Privacy Statement applies solely to the information collected on the Site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites. We encourage you to be aware when you are leaving this Site and read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that you visit before providing any personally identifiable information. 

**Changes to This Privacy Statement**  
We may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this privacy statement, we will notify you either by placing a prominent notice on the home page of our web site or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates. 

**Contact Information**  
If you have questions about our privacy statement or our use of your information, or if you need help changing your personal information, please contact us by sending e-mail to [hello@dotnet247.com](mailto:hello@dotnet247.com). WWWWWWWW WWWWWWWW WWWWWWWW WWWWWWWW WWWWWWWW WWWWWWWW WWWWWWWW WWWWWWWW WWWWWWWW WWWWWWWW WWWWWWWW WWWWWWWW WWWWWWWW WWWWWWWW WWWWWWWW WWWWWWWW
